var choices = [

    {
        question: "Which of these is a valid JavaScript comment?",
        answers: [
            "<!-- comment goes here -->",
            "// comment goes here",
            "///comment goes here",
            "::comment goes here",
     
       ],

        correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    },

    {
        question: "What is the preferred way to loop through an Array?",
        answers: [
            
            "for loop",
            "while loop",
            "list loop",
            "for ... of loop",
        
        ],

        correctAnswerIndex: 3,
    },

    
    {
        question: "The Document Object Model (DOM) is a hierarchy that most closely resembles what object?",
        answers: [
            "a spiderweb",
            " a castle",
            "a tree",
            "a tournament bracket",
        ],

        correctAnswerIndex: 2
    },


    {
        question: "How can we access the data attributes of an HTML element from within JavaScript?",
        answers: [
            "element.dataset",
            "element.getAttribute",
            "element.getData()",
            "element.fetchData()",
        
        ],
        correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    },

    {
        question: "What method allows us to add an attribute to a DOM element?",
        answers: [
            "element.getAttribute()",
            "element.createAttribute()",
            "element.setAttribute()",
            "element.makeAttribute()",
        
        ],

        correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    },

 

    {
        question: "Which of the following type of variable is visible everywhere in your JavaScript code?",
        answers: [
            "global variable",
            "local variable",
            "Both of the above",
            "None of the above.",
        ],

        correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    },

    {
        question: "To insert a JavaScript into an HTML page, which tag is used?",
        answers: [
            "<script=â€™javaâ€™>",
            "<script>",
            "<javascript>",
            "<js>",
        
        ],

        correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    },

    {
        question: "What JavaScript keyword declares a variable?",
        answers: [
            "if",
            "create",
            "var",
            "for",
        
        ],

        correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    },

    {
        question: "JavaScript is interpreted by ?",
        answers: [
            "Client",
            "Server",
            "Object",
            "None of the above",
        
        ],

        correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    },

    {
        question: "Using which statement is how you test for a specific condition. ",
        answers: [
        "Select",
        "If",
        "Switch",
        "For", 
            
        ],

        correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    },

]

